Guide to the Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 1927-1974
Ross, Philip Collection of NLRB Documents
- 21-CA-5549; Bay City Bearing Company, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 8)
- 21-CA-5550; L. A. Classic Company, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 9)
- 21-CA-5551; General Motors Corporation, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 10)
- 21-CA-5552; Lockhead Aircraft Co., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 11)
- 21-CA-5554; Screw Products Corporation of America, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 12)
- 21-CA-5555; Reynolds Metals Company, Can Division, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 13)
- 21-CA-5556; Globe Electrical Manufacturing Co., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 14)
- 21-CA-5558; Yellow Cab Company of Los Angeles, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 15)
- 21-CA-5560; Bab-Rand Company, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 16)
- 21-CA-5565; Myers Barrel, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 17)
- 21-CA-5567; Continental Device Corp., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 18)
- 21-CA-5568; Pacific Electricord Company, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 19)
- 21-CA-5568; Pacific Electricord Company, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 20)
- 21-CA-5572; Long Beach Marina Shipyard, Inc., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 21)
- 21-CA-5574; Dow Chemical Co., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 22)
- 21-CA-5575; General Tire & Rubber Company, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 23)
- 21-CA-5577; All Mailing Service, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 24)
- 21-CA-5581; P & H Trucking Company, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 25)
- 21-CA-5582; Coast Cartage Co., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 26)
- 21-CA-5584; Certified Electric, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 27)
- 21-CA-5585; Chevrolet Motors Division, GMC, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 28)
- 21-CA-5588; Snowflake Baking Co., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 29)
- 21-CA-5589; The Aerospace Corporation, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 30)
- 21-CA-5592; Stardust County Club, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 31)
- 21-CA-5593; Coolair Manufacturing Corporation, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 32)
- 21-CA-5595; Al Ortale Rambler, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 33)
- 21-CA-5596; Southern California Council of Public Employees, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 34)
- 21-CA-5597; Hughes Aircraft Co., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 35)
- 21-CA-5598; Olson Bros., Inc., 1963 (Box 230, Folder 36)
- 21-CA-5601; Hills Transportation Co., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 1)
- 21-CA-5603; Abco Hardware & Builders' Supply, Inc., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 2)
- 21-CA-5604; John Taft Electric Co., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 3)
- 21-CA-5610; Philips Industries of California, Inc., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 4)
  LaVerne, California
- 21-CA-5613; S & E Pipeline Construction, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 5)
- 21-CA-5615; Eastern Auto Parts Co., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 6)
- 21-CA-5616; Hoimes & Narver, Inc., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 7)
- 21-CA-5619; American Metaseal Company, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 8)
- 21-CA-5621; Marvin Electric Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 9)
- 21-CA-5623; Southern Tank Lines, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 10)
- 21-CA-5625; M & A Steel Co., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 11)
- 21-CA-5626; Sunset Cabinet Co., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 12)
- 21-CA-5627; Andrew California Corp., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 13)
- 21-CA-5629; Firestone Store, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 14)
- 21-CA-5630; Chevrolet Division, General Motors Corporation, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 15)
- 21-CA-5631; Chevrolet Division, General Motors Corporation, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 16)
- 21-CA-5637; Andrew California Corp., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 17)
- 21-CA-5638; Consolidated Novelty Co., Inc., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 18)
  Holly dale, California
- 21-CA-5650; Calorator Mfg. Co., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 19)
- 21-CA-5653; California Sand Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 20)
- 21-CA-5655; Rohr Corporation, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 21)
- 21-CA-5656; Leon Ames Ford, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 22)
- 21-CA-5668; A. S. Mason General Oilfield Construction, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 23)
- 21-CA-5683; Jack's at the Beach, 1963 (Box 231, Folder 24)
  Ocean Park, California
- 21-CA-5692; Bourns, Inc., 1963 (Box 231, Folder 25)
- 21-CA-5073; Treasure-Craft of California, 1962 (Box 232, Folder 1)
- 21-CA-5094; Rodney Stokes Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 232, Folder 2)
- 21-CA-5096; General Dynamics Corporation, Convair Division, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 3)
- 21-CA-5093; American Potash & Chemical Corp., 1963 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  Trona, California
- 21-CA-5069; Angeles Desk Co., 1962 (Box 232, Folder 5)
- 21-CA-5075; Electronic Enclosures, Inc., 1962 (Box 232, Folder 6)
- 21-CA-5078; Dewey Company, Inc., 1962 (Box 232, Folder 7)
- 21-CA-5077; Standard Oil Company of California, 1962 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  Western Operations, Inc.
- 21-CA-5098; Angeles Desk Company, 1963 (Box 232, Folder 9)
- 21-CA-5441; Todd Shipyards Corporation, 1962 (Box 232, Folder 10)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases Filed March, 1959 (Box 232, Folder 11)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases Filed June, 1959 (Box 232, Folder 12)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases Filed July, 1959 (Box 232, Folder 13)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases, Filed August, 1959 (Box 232, Folder 14)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases Filed April, 1959 (Box 232, Folder 15)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases Filed May, 1959 (Box 232, Folder 16)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-003, 1959 (Box 233, Folder 1)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0003, 1957-1958 (Box 233, Folder 2)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0003, 1955-1956 (Box 233, Folder 3)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0003, 1953-1954 (Box 233, Folder 4)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0003, 1948-1952 (Box 233, Folder 5)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1959 (Box 233, Folder 6)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1957-1958 (Box 233, Folder 7)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1955-1956 (Box 233, Folder 8)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1953-1954 (Box 233, Folder 9)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0004, 1948-1952 (Box 233, Folder 10)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0005, 1959 (Box 233, Folder 11)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0005, 1957-1958 (Box 233, Folder 12)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board, 1955-1956 (Box 233, Folder 13)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0005, 1953-1954 (Box 233, Folder 14)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board, 1948-1952 (Box 233, Folder 15)
- 12-RC-2508; Universal Cigar Corporation, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 1)
- 12-RC-2512; Wise Potato Chip Company, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  St. Augustine, Florida
- 12-RC-2550; Florida Machine Foundry Co., 1966 (Box 234, Folder 3)
- 10-CA-1117; Buford Hall and Smith, 1959 (Box 234, Folder 4)
- 12-RC-2484; Crest Leather Manufacturing Corporation, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 5)
- 12-RC-2501; ALCO Standard Corporation and RMF, Inc., 1966 (Box 234, Folder 6)
- 12-RC-2467; Scott Electronics Corporation, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 7)
- 12-CA-2213; Winn-Dixie Stores, Inc., 1965 (Box 234, Folder 8)
- State University of New York, 1969 (Box 234, Folder 9)
- 12-RC-2518; Key Biscayne Hotel & Villas, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 10)
  Key Biscayne, Florida
- 5-C3-700; Westing House Electric Corp, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 11)
  Linthicum, Maryland
- Background Categories for C and R Cases, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 12)
- 12-RC-2483; Redwing Carriers, Inc., 1966 (Box 234, Folder 13)
- 12-RC-2460; Singleton Packing Corporation, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 14)
- Report to the Industrial Union Department AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 15)
- Publications and Hearings before the Special Subcommittee on Labor of the Committee on Education and Labor House of Representatives, 1967 (Box 234, Folder 16)
  Congress, Washington, D. C.
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases Filed 1959 (Box 234, Folder 17)
- The George Washington Law Review, 1960 (Box 234, Folder 18)
  National Labor Relation Board, December, 1960
- The Growth of British Industrial Relations, 1960 (Box 234, Folder 19)
  E. H. Phelps Brown
- International Unionism a study in (No Suggestions) relations, 1967 (Box 234, Folder 20)
  John Crispo
- National Labor Relations Board N. L. R. B. Statistical Reports, 1964 (Box 234, Folder 21)
  Recommendations for Their Improvement, November, 1964
- Tennessee Law Review, 1954 (Box 234, Folder 22)
  The Law and Labor-Management Relations February 1954
- The Representative Bibliography of American Labor History, 1964 (Box 234, Folder 23)
  Maurice F. Neufeld
- French Magazines, 1968 (Box 234, Folder 24)
  L'Express, Paris Match
- Carlson Case, Interviews and Decision (bound), 1910 (Box 234, Folder 25)
- Fortran Coding Form, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 26)
  RC Region 38
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009, 1959 (Box 234, Folder 27)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009; 1957-1958 (Box 234, Folder 28)
  Washington D. C.
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board, 1955-1956 (Box 234, Folder 29)
  CA-0009; Washington, D. C.
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009, 1953-1954 (Box 234, Folder 30)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009, 1948-1952 (Box 234, Folder 31)
- Daily Labor News, 1971-1972 (Box 234, Folder 32)
- Labor Supply in the Construction Industry: A Case Study of Upstate New York, 1969 (Box 234, Folder 33)
  Howard G. Foster thesis draft
- Union-Caused Employee Discrimination Under the Taft-Hartley Act, 1964 (Box 234, Folder 34)
  B. L. Samoff
- Labor Relations Reporter, 1968 (Box 234, Folder 35)
  Bureau of National Affairs, Inc.
- U.S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009 1959-, Text (Box 235, Folder 1)
- U.S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009 1955-1956, Text (Box 235, Folder 2)
- U.S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009 1957-1958, Text (Box 235, Folder 3)
- U.S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009 1948-1952, Text (Box 235, Folder 4)
- U.S. National Labor Relations Board CA-0009 1953-1954, Text (Box 235, Folder 5)
- NLRB Coding Sheets, Text (Box 235, Folder 6)
- Bound volume of Committee Notes, 1910; Text (Box 235, Folder 7)
- Daily Labor News [1 of 2], Text (Box 235, Folder 8)
- Daily Labor News [2 of 2], Text (Box 235, Folder 9)
- Labor Supply in the construction Industry: A Case Study of Upstate NY by Howard G. Foster, March 1969 (Thesis Draft) [1 of 2], Text (Box 235, Folder 10)
- Labor Supply in the construction Industry: A Case Study of Upstate NY by Howard G. Foster, March 1969 (Thesis Draft) [2 of 2], Text (Box 235, Folder 11)
- Labor Relations Reporter / Labor Relations Expediter, Text (Box 235, Folder 12)
- Union - Caused Employee Discrimination under the Taft-Hartley Act / B.L. Samoff, 1964; Text (Box 235, Folder 13)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0000, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 1)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0001, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 2)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0002, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 3)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0003, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 4)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0004, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 5)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0005, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 6)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0006, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 7)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0007, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 8)
- U. S. National Labor Relations Board CB-0008, 1954-1959 (Box 236, Folder 9)
- 1-CB-601; United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local #88, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  Portsmouth, New Hampshire
- 1-CB-699; Penobscot Bay Longshoremen's Local 1519, 1961 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  Searsport, Maine
- 1-CB-602; Carpenters Local #853, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 2)
  Clinton, Massachusetts
- 1-CB-694; International Union United Automobile, Aircraft & Agricultural Implement Workers, 1963 (Box 237, Folder 2)
- 1-CB-748; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers Union, No. 25, 1963 (Box 237, Folder 3)
- 1-CB-609; Wood, Wire & Metal Lathers' International Union, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 3)
- 1-CB-610; Local 408 United Association of Plumbing & Pipefitting Industry, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 4)
- 1-CB-762; International United Automobile, Aerospace, Aircraft & Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1963 (Box 237, Folder 4)
  New Bedford, California
- 1-CB-611; Local 687, Brotherhood of Painters & Decorators, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 5)
- 1-CB-767; Hoisting and Portable Engineers, Local 4, 1963 (Box 237, Folder 5)
- 1-CB-612; Local 184 Bakery and Confectionery Workers, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 6)
- 1-CB-776; Local 1325; Retail Clerks International Association, 1963 (Box 237, Folder 6)
- 1-CB-613; International Typographical Union, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 7)
  Indianapolis, Indiana
- 1-CB-614; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, Helpers Local 671, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 8)
- 1-CB-615; Local 25, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 9)
- 1-CB-616; Local 170, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 10)
- 1-CB-617; Textile Workers Union of America Local No. 494, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 11)
  August, Maine
- 1-CB-619; Local 387, U. W. U. A. AFL-CIO Boston Edison Clerical Workers Union, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 12)
- 1-CB-622; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 13)
- 1-CB-623; Amalgamated Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen of North America, 1959 (Box 237, Folder 14)
- 1-CB-827; International Brotherhood of Pulp Sulphite & Paper Mill Workers, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  Groveton, New Hampshire
- 1-CB-827; International Brotherhood of Pulp Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  AFL-CIO, Local No. 61
- 1-CB-800; Construction and General Laborers Union, Local 230, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 3)
- 1-CB-804; 1-2 Carpenters Local 40, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 4)
- 1-CB-806; International Organization of Masters, Mates & Pilots Local 11, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 5)
- 1-CB-807; Local 573; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 6)
- 1-CB-812; Local 49, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 7)
- 1-CB-811; Local 295 of the Leather Workers International Union of America, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 8)
- 1-CB-812; Milk Wagon Drivers & Creamery Workers, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 9)
- 1-CB-813; Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, Local Union No. 481, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 10)
- 1-CB-814; Local 230, International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers Union of America, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 11)
- 1-CB-815; Local 230, International Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers Union of America, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 12)
- 1-CB-816; Local 182; International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, AFL CIO, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 13)
- 1-CB-817; Wood, Wire & Metal Lathers International Union Local 78, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 14)
- 1-CB-818; Local 42, Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers' International Union of America, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 15)
- 1-CB-819; International Brotherhood of Pulp Sulphite & Paper Mill Workers, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 16)
  Teaneck, New Jersey
- 1-CB-820; Taunton Leather Workers' Union, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 17)
- 1-CB-821; Local 1767; Painters - Paperhanging Union, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 18)
- 1-CB-822; International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 19)
- 1-CB-823; United Textile Workers of America & Local 19, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 20)
  New York
- 1-CB-824; Local 1505, Electrical Workers AFL CIO & Its Agent Andrew McGlinchey, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 21)
- 1-CB-826; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1505, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 22)
- 1-CB-828; Taunton Leather Workers Union, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 23)
- 1-CB-829; Bricklayers Benevolent and prot. Association, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 24)
- 1-CB-831; New England Petroleum Labor Organization, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 25)
  South Thomaston, Maine
- 1-CB-832; Gulf Employees Association of N. E., 1963 (Box 238, Folder 26)
- 1-CB-833; Brewery Workers Union, No. 8, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 27)
- 1-CB-834; Charter Oak Lodge No. 350, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 28)
- 1-CB-835; Local 407 United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 29)
- 1-CB-836; Local Union 1199, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 30)
- 1-CB-837; Local 443, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 1)
- 1-CB-839; United Mine Works of America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 2)
- 1-CB-840; United Mine Workers of America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 3)
- 1-CB-841; Local 1505, I. B. E. W., 1963 (Box 239, Folder 4)
- 1-CB-842; Teamsters, Local 443, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 5)
- 1-CB-843; Hoisting and Portable, Power Shovel and Dredge Engineers, Local 4, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 6)
- 1-CB-844; Construction & General Laborers Union, Local 385, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 7)
- 1-CB-845; Teamsters, Local Union 443, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 8)
- 1-CB-846; Local 215, International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 9)
- 1-CB-847; International Association of Machinists, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 10)
- 1-CB-849; Hoisting and Portable, Power Shovel and Dredge Engineers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 11)
- 1-CB-850; Local 1505, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 12)
- 1-CB-851; United Association of Journeymen & Apprentices of the Plumbing & Pipe Fitting Industry, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 13)
- 1-CB-852; Local 4, International Union of Operating Engineers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 14)
- 1-CB-853; Local 29, Boilermakers et al & William Manning, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 15)
- 1-CB-854; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, No. 677, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 16)
- 1-CB-855; United Bro. Of Carpenters & Joiners Local 624, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 17)
  Brocton, Massachusetts
- 1-CB-856; United Slate, Tile & Composition Roofers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 18)
- 1-CB-857; International Ladies Garmet Workers Union, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 19)
- 1-CB-858; Teamsters Local No. 443, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 20)
- 1-CB-859; Local 29, International Brotherhood of Boilermakers Iron Shipbuilders, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 21)
- 1-CB-860; Local 453, United Association of Journeymen & Apprentices of the Plumbing & Pipefitting Industry of the U. S. and Canada, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 22)
- 1-CB-861; International Union of Hod Carriers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 23)
- 1-CB-862; Local 2269 United Steelworkers of America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 24)
- 1-CB-863; United Automobile Aircraft Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 25)
- 1-CB-864; Construction and General Laborers Local 230, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 26)
- 1-CB-866; Moving Picture Machine Operators Local 223, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 27)
  Riverside, Rhode Island
- 1-CB-867; Bakers' Union Local No. 45, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 28)
- 1-CB-868; Local 1213, Hanover-Lebanon of the Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 29)
  Lebanon, New Hampshire
- 1-CB-869; Teamsters, Local No. 646, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 30)
- 1-CB-870; Amalgamated Lace Operatives of America, Lever Sect. and Amalgamated Lace Operative of America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 31)
  West Warwick and Providence, Rhode Island
- 1-CB-871; Amalgamated Lace Operatives of America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 32)
- 1-CB-872; United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO and its Agents Sidney Larsen and Herbert Gurney, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 33)
- 1-CB-873; Metropolitan Boston Salesmen's Union, Local 122, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 34)
- 1-CB-874; Teamsters, Local 526, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 35)
- 1-CB-875; Lewiston-Auburn Shoe Workers Protective Association, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 36)
- 1-CB-876; Pattern Makers. League of North America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 37)
- 1-CB-878; Hod Carriers and Laborers International Union, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 38)
- 1-CB-879; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 35, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 39)
- 1-CB-880; Local 1329, International Longshoremen's Association, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 40)
- 1-CB-881; District 50 United Mine Workers of America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 41)
- 1-CB-882; Massachusetts Race Track Employees Guild, Inc., 1963 (Box 239, Folder 42)
- 1-CB-884; International Association of Bridge Structural, & Ornamental. Iron Workers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 43)
- 1-CB-885; Springfield Typographical Union No. 216, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 44)
- 1-CB-886; Local 1505, International Brotherhood of Electric Workers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 45)
- 1-CB-887; United Association of Plumbing & its Local 217, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 46)
- 1-CB-889; International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 47)
- 1-CB-890; Hotel & Restaurant Employees & Bartenders Local 116, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 48)
- 1-CB-894; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 49)
- 1-CB-895; International Allicance of Theatrical & Stage Employees, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 50)
  New York City, New York
- 1-CB-896; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 1505, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 51)
- 1-CB-897; United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 239, Folder 52)
- 1-CB-1067; Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 1)
- 1-CB-1074; Sheetmetal Workers International Association, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 2)
- 1-CB-1007; Westfield, Etchers & Lithographers of Metal Printing Workers Union, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 3)
- 1-CB-1040; United Slate, Tile & Composition Roofers, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 4)
- 1-CB-1042; United Slate, Tile & Composition Roofers, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 5)
- 1-CB-1045; United Slate, Tile & Composition Roofers, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 6)
- 1-CB-1046; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 7)
- 3-CB-505; Local 294, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, et al, 1961 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  Vestal, New York
- 3-CB-601; Hotel & Restaurant & Bartenders International Union Local 136, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  Vernon Downs, NY
- 3-CB-613; Local Union Number 497, Affiliated with the United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe fitting Industry of the United States and Canada, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  Jacksonville, Alabama
- 3-CB-614; Hod Carriers' Building & Common Laborers' Union Local 7, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  West Corners, New York
- 3-CB-623; International Union of Operating Engineers Local 137, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  White Plains, New York
- 3-CB-624; Engineers Operating Local 17, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 6)
- 3-CB-625; Teamsters, Local 375, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 7)
- 3-CB-627; International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 106, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 8)
- 3-CB-628; Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 9)
- 3-CB-630; Bricklayers, Masons & Plasterers International, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 10)
- 3-CB-631; Machinists, Lodge No. 6, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 11)
- 3-CB-631; Machinists, Lodge No. 6, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 12)
- 3-CB-633; Mine Workers, Local 12330, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 13)
- 3-CB-633; Mine Workers of America, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 14)
- 3-CB-634; Hotel, Restaurant & Bartenders, Local 199, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 15)
- 3-CB-635; Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Food Employees Union, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 16)
- 3-CB-636; Bakery & Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, Local 16, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 17)
- 3-CB-637; Teamsters, Local 264, Bakery Drivers and Salesmen, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 18)
- 3-CB-638; Local 343, Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 19)
- 3-CB-639; Engineers, Operating, Local 410, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 20)
- 3-CB-639; Engineers, Operating, Local 410, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 21)
- 3-CB-639; Operating Engineers, Local 410, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 22)
- 3-CB-639; Engineers, Operating, Local 410, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 23)
- 3-CB-640; Hod Carriers, Local 7, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 24)
- 3-CB-642; Hod Carriers, Building & Common Laborers Union, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 25)
- 3-CB-642; Hod Carriers, Local 7, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 26)
- 3-CB-642; Hod Carriers, Local 7, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 27)
- 3-CB-643; Theatrical Stage Employees & Moving Picture Machine Operators of U. S. & Canada, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 28)
- 3-CB-644; Carpenters, Local 3211, AFL-CIO & Bus Agent Stanley Kozenewski, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 29)
  Herkimer, New York
- 3-CB-645; Teamsters, Local 317, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 30)